[
  {
    "id": 101,
    "question": "முன்னணி",
    "answers": ["முன்னணி"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 102,
    "question": "பரிந்துரை",
    "answers": ["பரிந்துரை"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 103,
    "question": "வரம்பு",
    "answers": ["வரம்பு"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 104,
    "question": "அரசியல்",
    "answers": ["அரசியல்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 105,
    "question": "நிரப்பு",
    "answers": ["நிரப்பு"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 106,
    "question": "உத்தரவு",
    "answers": ["உத்தரவு"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 107,
    "question": "கைவசம்",
    "answers": ["கைவசம்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 108,
    "question": "மெல்லினம்",
    "answers": ["மெல்லினம்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 201,
    "question": "கடைக்காரர்",
    "answers": ["கடைக்காரர்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 202,
    "question": "பெண்",
    "answers": ["பெண்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 203,
    "question": "தாத்தா",
    "answers": ["தாத்தா"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 204,
    "question": "நாற்காலி",
    "answers": ["நாற்காலி"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 205,
    "question": "மேசை",
    "answers": ["மேசை"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 206,
    "question": "காலணி",
    "answers": ["காலணி"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 207,
    "question": "கணினி",
    "answers": ["கணினி"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 208,
    "question": "சிறுவன்",
    "answers": ["சிறுவன்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 209,
    "question": "கழிவறை",
    "answers": ["கழிவறை"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 210,
    "question": "கைப்பை",
    "answers": ["கைப்பை"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 301,
    "question": "வாத்தியம்",
    "answers": ["வாத்தியம்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 302,
    "question": "திரைச்சீலை",
    "answers": ["திரைச்சீலை"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 303,
    "question": "நிலச்சரிவு",
    "answers": ["நிலச்சரிவு"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 304,
    "question": "நாட்டியம்",
    "answers": ["நாட்டியம்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 305,
    "question": "தொலைநோக்கி",
    "answers": ["தொலைநோக்கி"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 306,
    "question": "மன்னராட்சி",
    "answers": ["மன்னராட்சி"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 307,
    "question": "சமாதானம்",
    "answers": ["சமாதானம்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  },
  {
    "id": 308,
    "question": "கலைக்கூடம்",
    "answers": ["கலைக்கூடம்"],
    "score": 10,
    "additions":[]
  }
]
